but, What if we choose.
That you're the.
One to get us.
Tell me.
Do you believe in messages from dreams?
Do you believe in coincidence?
Oh, let.
Everything has its time.
What do you know?
Of the language of the stars.
The one they speak in silence.
Where a thousand stories have been told.
Time.
Just chance inside our destiny.
Look to it using.
Did someone already choose the road?
Or do we do it?
Maybe the answers
are meant to be found.
Maybe it's about choosing
who to invent a way.
Why? He betrayed us
when we can be the extras.
Used to watch life
passing by I'll take your hand
and change the perspective.
Okay.
What if we choose each other?
We choose each other.
We'll find your brand new destiny.
A brand new destiny.
We are the architects
of a brand new road.
What if we choose each other?
We choose each of us.
I'm with us today.
Oh, we choose
each other.
Tell me.
About the language of dreams.
Building an entire world.
What if we create new cities?
What if we travel through time?
Travel through other realities,
and build our own empires for life?
If you go to Mars, I'll stay home and.
Walk the dog.
What if we choose each other?
We choose each other.
We fight to bring you destiny.
We are the architects
of a brand new road.
What if we choose each other?
We choose each other.
Today
I'm no British.
This year we're better than
I will feel.
This.
Childhood.
Up to the door.
If that world doesn't exist,
we'll invented together.
It's the story.
It's been written.
We are the ones who choose it.
And if every day we discover
each other again.
We may.
I will build them
to an to me.
I will build.
You choose your way.
I choose you.
What if we choose each other?
We choose it today.
We're down to a brand new destiny.
A brand new destiny.
We are the architects
of a brand new road.
What if we choose each other?
We choose each other.
You an engineer?
And now we build up.
What? It?
Wixams each year.
What if we choose each other
under the law?
To the road.
To the road to one
doesn't exist within.
And two together.
To the other.
What if we choose each other?